const questions: Array<QuestionType> = [
    {
      question: "ὁ",
      answers: ["de", "het"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "ἡ",
      answers: ["de", "het"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "τό",
      answers: ["de", "het"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "ἀγάπη",
      answers: ["liefde"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "ἀρχή",
      answers: ["begin"],
      explanation: "(archaïsch)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "γῆ",
      answers: ["aarde", "land"],
      explanation: "(geografie, geologie)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "γραφή",
      answers: ["geschrift", "Heilige Schrift"],
      explanation: "(autograaf)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "διαθήκη",
      answers: ["bond"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "διδαχή",
      answers: ["leer"],
      explanation: "(Didache = Leer van de Twaalf Apostelen)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "δικαιοσύνη",
      answers: ["rechtvaardigheid"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "εἰρήνη",
      answers: ["vrede"],
      explanation: "(Irene)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "ἐντολή",
      answers: ["gebod"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "ἐπιστολή",
      answers: ["brief"],
      explanation: "(epistel)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "ζωή",
      answers: ["leven"],
      explanation: "(zoölogie)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "κεφαλή",
      answers: ["hoofd"],
      explanation: "(autocefaal)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "κώμη",
      answers: ["dorp"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "νεφέλη",
      answers: ["wolk"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "ὀργή",
      answers: ["toorn"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "παραβολή",
      answers: ["parabel", "gelijkenis"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "προσευχή",
      answers: ["gebed"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "συναγωγή",
      answers: ["synagoge"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "τιμή",
      answers: ["eer", "prijs"],
      explanation: "(timokratie)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "ὑπομονή",
      answers: ["standvastigheid"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "φυλακή",
      answers: ["gevangenis"],
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "φωνή",
      answers: ["geluid", "stem"],
      explanation: "(telefoon)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    },
    {
      question: "ψυχή",
      answers: ["ziel", "leven"],
      explanation: "(psychologie)",
      type: "woordenschat"
    }
]
const lesson8Vocabulary = {
  id: 'lesson8-vocabulary',
  name: 'Les 8 – Woordenschat', 
  active: false,
  questions
}
export default lesson8Vocabulary